There are barbs on the wheel of the lockbox
密码箱的滚轮上有倒刺
Notify the Identification Department
通知鉴定科
Come and check it out
过来检查一下
Is there any poison on it?
上面是否有毒剂
yes
是
How can one's conscience find out?
怎么 良心发现
Here comes a gift for me
给我送礼来了
Just pick
随便挑
Which one do you like, I’ll give you one
喜欢哪个送你一件
cool
酷
good
不错
This is for you
这个送你了
Suddenly he was so nice to me
突然对我这么好
There must be a conspiracy
肯定有阴谋
No conspiracy
没什么阴谋
That's what I plan to do
我呀 就是打算
to my life
对我的人生
Re-plan
重新规划一下
you won't want
你不会要
Marry that girl
跟那女孩结婚吧
what did you say
你说什么呢
Do you want it or not?
你到底要不要
Don't let me go to the market and sell everything
不要我到市场上全卖了
Of course I want it
要 当然要了
Buy one hand and sell it immediately at a high price
倒一手立马高价卖出去
so
所以啊
I can't sell you the original price either
我也不能原价卖你
Make a price
开个价吧
So anxious
这么着急
50% off the original price and transfer immediately
原价五折 立刻转账
Extremely anxious
急得不行
make a deal
成交
You must be in trouble
你肯定是遇到难处了
Otherwise, it would be impossible to sell equipment
不然也不可能卖装备
But if you don't want to say it
不过你要不愿意说
I can't help you much
我也帮不上什么忙
These props
这些道具
Someday you want to take it back
哪天你想拿回去
I'll redeem it for you at the purchase price
我按买的价格赎给你
floret
小花
you are so good to me
你对我这么好
I do not even know
我都不知道
How should I repay you?
该怎么报答你了
I don't need it
老铁 不需要
Let me give you a piece of advice
我给你个忠告
if someone invites you
如果有人邀请你
Participate in offline tasks
去参加线下任务
Don't answer it
千万别接
Remember
切记
Why
为什么啊
Because that's a trap
因为那是陷阱
Will make you bankrupt
会让你倾家荡产
Look at what I have now
你看我现在这些东西
It's all given to you
都抵给了你
You don’t want it to be like this, right?
你不想也变成这样吧
Don't want to at all
一点也不想
So be sure to remember
所以一定要记住
Never disconnect tasks
千万别接线下任务
understand
懂了吗
good
乖
meet again
又见面了
It’s easy for me to feel like this
你这样我很容易觉得
you are following me
你在跟踪我
No
没有
This bar is owned by my friend
这个酒吧是我朋友开的
Nothing
没什么事
I'll stay here
我就在这儿待着
Yeah
是吗
Mainly last time we met
主要上次见面
I didn’t get to chat with you more.
也没能跟你多聊几句
How have you been these past two years?
这两年过得还好吗
good
还行
This bar is good
这家酒吧不错的
do you come here often
你经常过来吗
Occasionally
偶尔吧
Do you work nearby?
在附近工作吗
Internet company next door
隔壁的互联网公司
That boy last time
那上次那个男孩
He's a colleague from your company, right?
是你公司的同事是吧
You have too many questions, right?
你问题也太多了吧
Are you still playing that game?
那个游戏还玩吗
No more playing
不玩了
Just don't play
不玩就好
game life days
游戏人生的日子
When will it be the first time?
什么时候是个头啊
Just don't play
不玩就对了
Actually, it happened before
其实之前的事吧
I'm here to drink
我是来喝酒的
I don’t want to mention other things
别的事情不想提
What if you want to drink
如果你想喝呢
Just a few drinks between the two of us
我们两个就喝几杯
other things
其他的事情
Just stop talking, okay?
就不要再说了好吗
Jamray
杰姆瑞
Bring me my bottle of wine
把我的存酒拿过来
Actually what do you have
其实你有什么
Unhappy incident
不开心的事
You can really tell me
你真的可以跟我讲
Because we have
因为咱们已经
Haven’t seen each other for so many years
那么多年没见了
I don't know your life
我并不了解你的生活
He can be considered an outsider.
也算是个局外人吧
Is it an emotional thing?
感情的事吗
You seem to care about my affairs
你好像很关心我的事
actually
其实
After returning from the United States
从美国回来之后
I just realized that there are many things
我才意识到有很多事情
I can't let go
是我放不下的
Yeah
是吗
Then I'm definitely not among them
那我肯定不在其中
you said
你说了
You don’t want to mention the past
你不愿意提以前的事
I don't want to mention it either
我也不愿意提
But we can meet again
可是咱们能再次遇见
It shows that there is still fate
说明还是有缘分的
Why don't we just meet this time?
不如就把这次相遇
Think of it as a new acquaintance between the two of us
当成咱们俩的重新认识
what do you think
你觉得怎么样
Don't waste any time
别费工夫了
And me
我呢
I already have someone I like
已经有喜欢的人了
Is it the boy from last time?
是上次那个男孩吗
no
不是
My order has been purchased
我的单已经买过了
Just stop wasting your time
你就不要再浪费时间
on me
在我身上了
you have been abandoned
你已经被抛弃了
professor
教授
right
对
I am the professor
我就是教授
Change to Yu Xiaoyue’s sample
换走于潇玥的样本
Is it you too?
也是你吗
it's me
是我
This was all arranged by them
这都是他们安排的
The one who threatens Yu Xiaoyue
那威胁于潇玥的
Where is Professor Li?
李教授呢
also me
也是我
why do you want to hurt her
你为什么要害她
harm her
害她
She wants to be an internet celebrity
她想做网红
How can it be that easy?
哪有那么容易啊
Operation and promotion require money
运营推广都需要钱
I'm here to help her make money
我是为了帮她挣钱
I just got into the spy game
才去接触特工游戏的
I want a cup of frozen lemon tea
要一杯冻柠茶
OK
好的
Complete offline tasks
完成线下任务
you can make more money
你可以赚更多的钱
to make more money
为了挣更多的钱
I came into contact with offline tasks
我就接触了线下任务
Taken photos of the laboratory
拍摄了实验室的照片
But when I react
可等我反应过来的时候
It's too late
已经来不及了
Also with my help
也是在我的帮助下
She became an internet celebrity
她成了网红
Fire
火了
But you want to leave me
可却要离开我
So you take her
所以你就把她
Also pulled down the water
也拉下了水
The best way to keep her
留住她最好的办法
Just destroy her
就是毁了她
Let her become like me
让她变成跟我一样的人
Boss Zhang gave me this advice
张老板这么指点我
do this
这么做的
She is because of you
她是因为你
No access to B13 samples at all
根本接触不到B13样本
That’s why you harmed Xiaoyue
才让你害于潇玥的
You two really have the same chemistry.
你俩还真是臭味相投啊
Have you met Boss Zhang?
见过张老板吗
We've only met in games
我们只在游戏中见过面
Were there any other contacts?
还有其他接触吗
she is cautious
她很谨慎
we only had one phone call
我们只通过一次电话
The sound is relatively neutral
声音比较中性
It should be a voice changer
应该是用的变声器
But sometimes she makes mistakes
但是她有疏漏的时候
What
什么
I can confirm that Boss Zhang
我能确定张老板
Just in Jinhai
就在津海
how do you know
你怎么知道
Have you heard the bells of Nam Van Harbor?
你听过南湾港的钟声吗
When I was on the phone with Boss Zhang
我跟张老板通话的时候
heard this bell
听到了这个钟声
Our campus is right there
我们园区就在那儿
I'm familiar with this bell
这个钟声我很熟悉
So Boss Zhang
所以张老板
Just in Jinhai Nanwan District
就在津海南湾区
At least follow me
至少跟我
She was there during the call
通话的时候她在
What do you think of this person?
你觉得这个人
Will I be by your side?
会在你身边吗
The proprietress of Yuyue Japanese Food Shop
渔樾日料店的老板娘
Is it related to the spy game?
跟特工游戏有关联吗
she
她
Not possible
没有可能吧
But I'm sure
但是我能确定
person who delivers the sample
传递样本的人
He's the owner of a seafood shop
是海鲜店的老板
i have seen him
我见过他
The sample is placed
样本就是放到
on his car
他的车上的
I always thought
我一直以为
Boss Zhang is only in the game
张老板只是游戏里面的
avatar
一个虚拟人物
But I didn't expect that she would be in Jinhai
可是没想到她就在津海
this for us
这对我们来说
is good news
是个好消息
Qin Chu
秦处
I recommend
我建议
temporarily blocked
暂时封锁
News of Shi Lei's rescue
石磊获救的消息
He knows Han Jie’s identity
他知道韩杰的身份
This is in our hands
这是我们手里
The most important clue
最重要的一条线索
I have informed the institute
我已经通知研究所
Let them post the obituary
让他们发讣告
Shi Lei was announced dead
宣布石磊不治身亡
I hope
我希望吧
I hope this news
我希望这个消息
capable of deterring spies
能够打消间谍的
doubt
疑虑
There is also news from the customs
海关那边也有消息
Han Jie recently declared
韩杰最近申报了
a batch of seafood
一批海鲜
To be shipped to Macau
要发往澳门
The receiving party is still the same as last time
接货方还是上回
The company that accepted the sample
接受样本的那家公司
They have something again
他们又有东西
About to send it out
要送出去了
Now that Boss Zhang is in control
张老板既然掌控了
The overall situation of Jinhai
整个津海的全局
She will definitely contact Han Jie
她必然会跟韩杰联系
Han Jie’s mobile phone and game account
韩杰手机和游戏账号
we keep staring
我们一直盯着
Han Jie has never been online
韩杰一直都没上线
It doesn't seem to be related to anything
好像也没和什么
suspicious person contact
可疑的人联系
but i doubt
但是我怀疑
He may have more than one cell phone
他可能不止一部手机
Or maybe he still has
也或者他可能还有
Other contact information
其他的联系方式
So you should pay close attention
所以你们要密切关注
Han Jie’s movements
韩杰的动向
He could be at any time
他随时都有可能
There are new actions
有新动作
clear
明白
How is the situation over there with Huang Zicheng?
黄子诚那边情况怎么样
Haven't replied to me yet
还没给我回复
But I will continue to follow up
但是我会继续跟进的
He cracked the secret agent mission for us
他对我们破获特工任务
Still very helpful
还是很有帮助的
Hello
喂
Shi Lei is dead
石磊死了
sure
确定吗
Obituaries issued by the institute
研究所发的讣告
Good to know
好 知道了
I am at home
我在家呢
And you
你呢
correct
对了
Do me a favor tomorrow
明天你帮我个忙
no problem
没问题
Where is this yacht club?
这个游艇会呢
It’s the whole Jinhai
是整个津海
The largest yacht club
最大的游艇会
Mr. Fang has arrived
方总已经到了
Let me introduce to you
我给大家介绍一下
Fang Lu
方陆
Come
来
Let me introduce
我介绍一下
This is Mr. Fang
这位是方总
He is currently in Jinhai
他呢 现在正在津海
Preparing to build a private art museum
筹建一座民营美术馆
Where are these two?
这两位呢
is the odyssey art foundation
是奥德赛艺术基金会
Overseas development manager
海外发展负责人
Good morning sir
你好 先生
everything fine
一切都好吗
everything is fine
一切都好
That's good
那就好
Please entertain me
你招待一下啊
I'll go to the kitchen and have a look
我去厨房看看
good
好
please
请
Thanks
谢谢
Do you want to try it?
要不要尝尝
How about it
怎么样
marvelous
太棒了
correct
对了
How is the seafood I ordered?
我订的海鲜怎么样了
Do not worry
放心吧
what you want
你要的东西
I picked them all myself
都是我亲自挑的
Thanks
谢谢
between us
咱俩之间
Don't be so polite
不用那么客气吧
Thanks for your hard work, Boss Han cooked the food himself.
辛苦韩老板亲自下厨了
Always borrow Mr. Chen’s yacht
总是借陈总的游艇
Go fishing
出海钓鱼
Is it appropriate to do some work?
干点活是应该的嘛
Mr. Han just went fishing
韩总刚出海钓的
Do you want to try it?
要不要试一下
OK
好啊
have a taste
尝尝
How about it
怎么样
It melts in your mouth
入口即化啊
Thanks to Brother Han
多亏了韩大哥
How can I have such a good taste?
我才能有如此口福啊
Him
他呀
But tuna enthusiast
可是金枪鱼发烧友
I went abroad to study
特意到国外去学过
This split fish for him
这分割鱼对他来说
Just a kind of enjoyment
就是一种享受
Then my brother and I are pretty much the same
那我跟哥哥可差不多
the only difference
唯一的区别
I am the one who eats fish
就是我把吃鱼
as a kind of enjoyment
当成一种享受
Really good
真行
How was the conversation above?
上面聊得怎么样了
I feel very good
我觉得挺好的
It's almost time for us to set sail.
那差不多咱们就开船吧
Okay, I'll do it right away
好 我这马上
Good to go
好 走
Walk
走
what did you eat
你吃什么
It's all fine
都可以啊
Do you think this one is okay?
这家你觉得行吗
Then sit down
那坐吧
If you are allergic, why don't you feed the cat?
过敏 你还去喂猫
The more dangerous things are
越是危险的事
The more people want to get closer
就越让人想靠近
That's why we
所以我们才会
Meet in the agent game
在特工游戏里相遇
Don’t you regret it?
不后悔吗
No regrets
不后悔啊
There is no point in regretting
后悔没什么意义
the most important
最重要的
is to solve the problem
是解决问题
How to solve it
怎么解决啊
The problem is not as serious as you think
问题没你想的那么严重
I've already asked
我已经问过了
without knowing it
在不知情的情况下
make mistakes
犯错误
There will be no heavy sentence
不会重判的
But no
可是没有
Help from both of us
我们两个人的帮助
those people behind
背后那些人
Can't get anything either
也拿不到东西
And last night
而且昨天晚上
I've checked
我已经查过了
This is our situation
咱俩这种情况
Even if it is a joint crime
就算是共同犯罪
do you know
你知道吗
Look
你看啊
People who enter Dr. Feng’s room
进冯博士房间的人
It's me
是我吧
The person who plugs the USB flash drive into the computer
把优盘插在电脑上的人
also me
也是我
I am also the accomplice
共犯也是我啊
I did it all by myself
都是我一个人干的
You are just playing games
你呀 只是在玩游戏
What am I going in for?
我进去干什么
You don't know either
你也不知道
But I know
可是我知道啊
Then forget about before
那就忘掉之前
Our conversation
我们的对话啊
stop talking
别再说
Already know about the spy mission
已经知道间谍任务
Such nonsense
这种傻话了
this is for you
这给你
what do you mean
你什么意思啊
You're not worried
你不是担心
Game binding credit card
游戏绑定信用卡
Will the credit be deducted?
会扣除信用金吗
Here is one hundred thousand dollars
这里是十万块钱
This is me
我这人啊
I usually don’t have any savings.
平时也没什么积蓄
all of a sudden
一时之间
I can only get so much
只能弄到这么多
It was Jiang Xiaohua who helped me
还是姜小花帮我的
But
可是
You listen to me first
你先听我说完
I don't know
我不知道呢
How much money is tied to your credit card?
你信用卡绑了多少钱
Where is the money?
这些钱呢
It may not be enough
也可能不够
But your ability and academic qualifications
但是你的能力和学历
Not bad at all
一样都不差
Not playing games
不玩游戏
You can definitely make money
肯定也能赚到钱
so
所以
can you exit the game
你能退出游戏吗
I can't accept it
我不能收
why
为什么呀
no reason
没有为什么
I can't take your money
我不能拿你的钱
Just think I borrowed it from you
你就当是我借你的
When will you have money?
你什么时候有钱
When will you pay me back?
你什么时候还我
Isn’t it over?
不就完了吗
I just hope you can understand
我只是希望你能明白
The spy's grip
间谍手里掌握的把柄
Not a threat to you
威胁不到你
And money can solve things
而且钱能解决的事情
It's not a big trouble
也不是什么大麻烦
But this game
但是这游戏啊
You must not play anymore
你千万不能再玩了
If you keep playing
你要是再玩下去
My whole life is ruined
整个人生就全毁了
But in your case
可是你的情况
Not much better than me
也比我好不到哪儿去啊
Didn’t you also bind the card?
你不是也绑定了卡吗
Don't worry about me
你别担心我
I have a way
我有办法
any solution
什么办法
Eat old age
啃老
good
好
I promise you
我答应你
exit the game
退出游戏
Very good
太好了
Then give your bank card
那你把银行卡
you wait later
你待会儿
Don't be so naive
你别那么单纯
In that game
那游戏里边
Which offline player is innocent?
哪个线下玩家是单纯的
Including your partner
包括你那个搭档
no
不是
You just said it casually
你这是随口一说呀
I still really think there is something wrong with Yao Yao
还是真觉得姚瑶有问题
Did you persuade her to quit the game?
你劝她退出游戏了吗
I guess she won't withdraw
我猜她就不会撤出来
This is an IOU
这是借条
I owe you the money
钱算我欠你的
OK
好的
The boss orders
老板 点菜
Two bottles of beer
来两瓶啤酒
coming
来了
let's celebrate
我们庆祝一下
What's there to celebrate?
这有什么可庆祝的
I'm really afraid that you will reject me
我真怕你拒绝我
If she really has a problem
如果她真的有问题的话
She should always be
她应该会一直
Just keep playing, right?
坚持玩下去 对吧
you don't know very well
你不是很了解
Is this the secret agent world?
这特工世界吗
people there
那里的人
All have different faces
都有不同的面孔
Not so easy to distinguish
没那么容易分清
Who is the big bad wolf and who is the little white rabbit?
谁是大灰狼谁是小白兔
You're not talking about those people
你不是说那些人
Are they all here for you?
都是冲着你来的吗
What if they come to you again?
如果他们再找你怎么办
do not worry about me
别担心我
I can deal with them
我有办法应付他们
any solution
什么办法
them
他们啊
It must be what happened before
肯定就是拿之前的事
threaten me
威胁我
It's really not possible
实在不行
I reported this to my boss
我就把这张老板举报了
Anyway, she was the one responsible for both of us.
反正咱们俩也是她害的
I can't find Boss Zhang
我找不着张老板
Then the National Security Bureau will definitely find her.
那国安局肯定能找着她
When the time comes
到时候啊
I can still be considered guilty and meritorious.
我还算是戴罪立功
Definitely get a lighter punishment
肯定从轻处罚
Come
来
cheers
干杯
end our gaming career
结束我们的游戏生涯
You won't regret it, will you?
你不会后悔了吧
I'll log it off now
我现在就把它注销
Won't you come together?
你不一起吗
Together
一起
The professor is out of control
教授已经不受控制了
It's no shame to get rid of it
除掉没什么可惜
At least you can use him
至少可以利用他
To draw the attention of Guoan
来引开国安的视线
Keep our more important people
保住我们更重要的人
He is still sleeping
他目前还在沉睡期
when necessary
必要的时候
i will wake him up
我会唤醒他
Your other Kingsman
你的另一个王牌特工
how's it going
进展得如何
Huang Zicheng and Yao Yao
黄子诚和姚瑶
Log out of the game
注销游戏了
Don't worry
不用担心
I will find a way
我会想办法的
Hello
喂
Zicheng
子诚
Your father fainted
你爸爸晕倒了
I'll take him to the hospital now
我现在就把他送医院去
What's up with him
他怎么了
The situation is not clear yet
情况还不清楚
You'd better come here quickly
你最好赶紧过来
I am coming over now
我马上过来
What's the matter?
什么事啊
Something happened to my dad
我爸出事了
Then I'll go with you
那我陪你一起去吧
No big problem
没什么大问题
Have a good rest
好好休息啊
thank you doctor
谢谢医生
doctor
医生
How is my dad doing?
我爸情况怎么样了
High blood pressure caused by excessive fatigue
过度疲劳引起的高血压
The condition is now under control
现在病情已经控制住了
That
那
Is the situation serious?
情况严重吗
Not serious
不算严重
But in the future
但以后呀
Be sure to take a rest
一定要注意休息
Don't let him get emotional
别让他情绪啊
Don’t be too nervous and get tired
过于紧张 不要疲劳
Okay, I will supervise him
行 我会监督他的
Observe for two days
观察两天
no problem
没什么问题
You can be discharged from the hospital
就可以出院了
Thank you thank you doctor
谢谢 谢谢医生
This matter
这事啊
I also have a responsibility
我也有责任
What’s your work schedule these days?
最近几日工作日程呢
relatively tight
比较紧
last night
昨天晚上
I stayed up all night
还熬了一个大夜
I just forgot to look
我就忘了看
His physical condition is gone
他的身体状况了
Don't blame yourself too much
你别太自责
No one can control him
没人能管得了他
OK
行
Then I'll go get Mr. Huang's medicine first.
那我就先去给黄总拿药
I'm leaving
先走了
Okay, don't worry anymore
好了 你别担心了
The doctor also said it's nothing serious
医生也说了没什么大事
That
那
Come in and stay with your uncle.
你快进去陪陪叔叔吧
I'll leave first
我就先走了
thank you
谢谢你啊
Gone
走了啊
Still pretending
还装
Where am I?
我这是在哪儿啊
I said you are so old
我说你这么大岁数了
Why else are you staying up late?
你还熬什么夜啊
I thought I was young
还以为自己年轻呢
Is it okay now?
现在好了吧
The doctor told you to be hospitalized
医生让你必须住院
have a good rest
好好休息
The doctor just said
医生刚才说
I'm fine
我没什么大碍
Didn't you just wake up?
你不是刚醒吗
What did the doctor say?
怎么医生说什么
You all know
你都知道啊
I'm telling you, you
我跟你说啊 你呀
Just take this opportunity
就借着这个机会啊
give me good
给我好好地
Get a general check-up
做一个全身性的检查
Did you hear that?
听见了吗
There is another meeting on the weekend
周末还有个会呢
Let's talk about it when I come back
等我回来再说吧
Just now
刚才
Who is that girl?
那个女孩是谁啊
Are you okay?
你到底有事没事啊
The eyes are pretty good
眼神还挺好使
when i
我什么时候
Don't let your guard down
都不能放松警惕
A friend of mine
我一朋友
How did we know each other?
怎么认识的
We met while playing games
玩游戏认识的啊
I see
我知道了
That's the one
就是那个
An unreliable game
不靠谱的游戏呗
I said can you have a good rest?
我说你能不能好好休息
Stop worrying about me every day
别天天为我瞎操心了
You run around every day
你天天跑东跑西的
Not even a serious job
连个正经工作都没有
Can I not worry?
我能不操心吗
How old are you?
你都多大了
Can you put that game away?
能不能把那游戏放一放
That game
那游戏啊
I'm really tired of playing
我还真玩腻了
I'm going to play a new one now
我现在打算玩一新的
Challenge upgrades are more exciting
挑战升级更刺激
do you think
你是不是觉得
I've lived too long
我活得太久了
Can you learn from your brother?
你能不能像你哥学学啊
I just plan to be like him
我就是打算向他看齐
Let's go together
我们俩一起呀
Do a big job
干一票大的
What's the meaning
什么意思
Just kidding you
逗你呢
You little bastard
你这个小兔崽子
Are you kidding me?
你逗我呢
I have informed
我已经通知
Gao Tianyang is here
高天阳过来了啊
when
什么时候
I'll probably be there soon.
估计一会儿就到了吧
Just wait to be scolded.
你就等着挨骂吧你
I suddenly feel sleepy
我突然好困
I want to sleep for a while
我要睡一会儿
Don't let him come
你别让他来了啊
I have nothing to do
我没什么事
Let Xiao Liu
下午就让小刘
Sent me back
送我回去了
You should have a good rest.
你好好休息吧你
Okay, okay, okay
行行行 行了
Let's go, let's go
走 走吧 走吧
How about it
怎么样
He is still me
他还是我啊
he
他
Nothing's wrong with him
他没什么事
I heard you are coming
听说你要来了
Go to sleep quickly
赶快就睡了
Let him have a good rest
让他好好休息休息吧
don't bother him
别去打扰他
go out and chat
出去聊聊
Let's go
走吧
elder brother
哥
You know my childhood dream
你知道我小时候的梦想
What is it?
是什么吗
what
什么呀
Superman
超人
save the earth
拯救地球
still
还是
Boss
大佬
Dominate the world
制霸江湖
so
所以啊
I've thought about it
我想好了
I have to help you
我得帮你们
Kill them
把他们给灭了
Give the game a pure land
还游戏一片净土
Huang Zicheng
黄子诚
This is not a joke
这 这不是在开玩笑啊
I mean everything I said
我说的都是认真的
you
你
you know what you have to face
你知道自己要面对的
What is it?
是什么吗
Not in your game
不是你游戏里的
What villain?
什么大反派
is a real spy
是真正的间谍
I know
我知道
They dragged me into the water
他们拉我下水
Is it just for Lao Huang?
无非就是为了老黄吗
Then I have to go even more
那我就更得去了
If I don't go
我要是不去
They also have to replace them with someone else
他们也得换别人
Lao Huang's physical condition
老黄那身体状况
you saw it too
你也看见了
I'll get hurt by mistake again.
回头再让人给误伤了
In this case
既然这样
Then I have to go even more
那我就更得去了
But
但是吧
Where am I now?
我现在呢
Encountered a little trouble
遇到点小麻烦
that is
就是
My game account has been canceled
我那个游戏账号注销了
Do you think they can still find me?
你说他们还能找我吗
Logged out
注销了
Not just to test Yao Yao
还不是为了测试姚瑶
Advise her to quit the game
劝她退出游戏
Unexpectedly, she logged out
结果没想到她注销了
Then I do it for
那我为了
Do not arouse her suspicion
不引起她的怀疑
I can only log out as well.
也只能跟着注销了
You have to admit it this time
这回你得承认
Did you make a mistake in your judgment?
你判断错误了吧
Don’t you talk about Yao Yao
你不说人姚瑶
Won't you quit the game?
不会退出游戏吗
Who told you to act without permission?
谁让你擅自行动的呀
I said you are still in the game
我说你 你还游戏里的
What about you, Kingsman?
王牌特工呢你
madness
愚蠢
Not that me
不是 那我
You just can't do it at all
你就完全就做不了
real world agents
现实世界的特工
You don't know at all
你根本就不清楚
What are you facing?
你到底面对的
What is it
是什么东西
Your little move
你的一丁点的举动
you can cause
你就能导致
All plans shattered
全盘计划破灭
The anti-Japanese struggle is so cruel
反间斗争就是这么残酷
I can't tolerate any of your worries
容不下你任何的牵挂
I can't tolerate those of yours either
也容不下你那些
childish emotions
幼稚的情感
no
不是
Then tell me
那你告诉我
How can I be one
怎么才能当一个
qualified agent
合格的特工
Just like you
就都像你这样呗
you knew it early
你很早就知道
I'm playing that game
我在玩那个游戏了
You know that game is dangerous
你知道那游戏很危险
but didn't tell me
却不告诉我
Even if you are my brother
即便你是我哥
yes
是
If that's the case
那要是这样的话
You are really one
你还真是一个
qualified agent
合格的特工
sorry
对不起
i can never do it
我永远做不了
people like you
像你这样的人
but i tell you
但是我告诉你
Just wait and see
你等着瞧
If I become an agent
我要是当上特工
Definitely better than you
肯定比你强
Huang Zicheng asked Yao Yao
黄子诚让姚瑶
Canceled account
注销账号了
He went to test Yao Yao
他去试探姚瑶去了
smart-aleck
自作聪明
It's really wrong to make decisions without permission
擅自作主确实不对
But he has a very positive attitude
但他态度很积极啊
There is no point in being active.
积极有个屁用啊
I don't need him to be active
我不需要他积极
I grew up with him
我跟他从小一起长大
I can't hold back his character.
他那个性格我都按不住
You said it sounds nice
你说好听了
Passion and friendship
热血 重情谊
You need to be involved in the anti-Japanese struggle
你要放在反间斗争中
Just this kind of behavior
就这种举动
You can die at any time
随时都可以送命
So you start from the beginning
所以你从一开始
I didn't want him to get involved
就没想让他卷进来
right
对不对
Things pushed him to
事情把他推到
This position is up
这个位置上了
He must bear it
他必须得担起
This responsibility
这份责任啊
But he hasn't realized it yet
但是他还没有意识到
danger of things
事情的危险
He met Boss Zhang
他见的张老板
It’s all in the game
全是在游戏里边的
on the Internet
网络上的
He doesn't know at all
他根本就不知道
this fight
这场斗争
real dangers faced
所面临的真正危险
But he is very smart
但是他很聪明啊
He knows we are protecting him
他知道有我们在保护他
So he is not afraid at all
所以他根本就不害怕
You can do it
你行了吧
I know him better than you
我比你了解他
He's just a conceited agent.
他就是一个自负的特工
He simply can't do it
他根本就做不到
The task we gave him
我们给他的任务
I'll help you train him
我帮你调教调教他
I'm not as pessimistic as you
我没你那么悲观
He can only see a corner
他只能看到一角
And we can see it all
而我们能看见全部
I have confidence in him
我对他有信心
Believe me
相信我
Do you still like to play this?
你还喜欢打这个
I want to fight now
我现在就想打架
Come
来
how do you feel
感觉怎么样
Dissatisfied
不服
I wasn't ready just now
刚才我没准备好
Come again
再来
So how do you feel now?
那现在感觉怎么样
Impressed
服了
have a drink together
一起喝一杯
good
好
This place is really nice
这地儿真不错啊
It must be extremely difficult to make an appointment
肯定特难预约吧
Nothing I choose is wrong
我选的东西都不会错
I'll hang out with you after it's settled
妥了 以后就跟你混了
your martini
您的马天尼
your mojito
您的莫吉托
Thanks
谢谢
alcohol free
不含酒精
How do you know I like to drink this?
你怎么知道我爱喝这个
Your brother said that
你哥说的
My brother goes back
我哥回去
I won't tell you anymore
不会跟你说了
A lot of bad things about me, right?
不少我的坏话吧
All good words
都是好话
Hot-blooded boy
热血男孩
It doesn't sound like it
听起来可真不像
You don't need to worry about him
你不用管他
I think you did a very good job
我觉得你做得非常好
You really think so
你真是这么想的
Positive attitude towards work
对工作 态度积极
Be affectionate and loyal to friends
对朋友 重情重义
Still you understand me
还是你懂我
If I had known earlier, I would have talked to you directly.
那早知道我直接跟你谈
Isn’t it over?
不就完了吗
But there is one thing
但是有一点
Since you agreed to cooperate with us
既然同意了跟我们合作
Discipline comes first
纪律是第一位
Our work
我们的工作
It’s different from playing games with you
和你玩游戏不一样
No chance to do it again
没有再来一次的机会
any move
任何举措
All must be discussed
都必须要商量着来
no one
没有任何一个人
Can be a lone hero
能当孤胆英雄
Then can I discuss it with you directly?
那我能直接跟你商量吗
i think you speak
我觉得你说话
It's more palatable than him
都比他顺耳
Okay
行啊
Any instructions received in the future
以后接到任何指示
Contact me as soon as possible
第一时间跟我联系
sure
可以啊
but other things
但是其他的事
No need to report it, right?
不用汇报了吧
Things other than work
工作以外的事
Of course not
当然不用了
For example, you have been secretly paying attention to
比如你一直偷偷关注
Those two pretty girls behind me
我背后那两个漂亮姑娘
Okay, Sister Xi
可以啊 熙姐
Who doesn’t like to see beautiful women?
美女谁不爱看啊
You
你啊
Nothing like Guoan's
一点都不像国安的
What is the national security like?
国安什么样啊
National security
国安的
I think it should be
我觉着都应该是
Like Gao Tianyang
高天阳那样
When you talk to me
找我谈话的时候
Not an underground garage
不是地下车库
It's a place for senior citizens to hang out
就是老年人活动的地方
He can compare with me
他能跟我比
That's far from it
那差远了
Don't understand life
不懂生活
It's quite tiring to work with him, right?
跟他工作挺累的吧
I can't help myself
身不由己啊
Too
也是
You said I have such a brother
你说我摊上这么一哥
But he is this person
但他这人啊
Usually pretty good
平时还挺好
As soon as I start working
就是一工作起来
It's like a different person
跟换了个人似的
Because he is worried about you
因为他担心你
you haven't seen it yet
你还没有见过
The cruelty of the struggle
斗争的残酷
You made a wrong move
你一步踏错
Not just a total loss
不仅仅是全盘皆输
even sacrifice
甚至会牺牲
He is really worried about you
他是真的很担心你
when i go out
我出门的时候
He also warned me
他还叮嘱我呢
Really
真的吗
certainly
当然
he knows
他知道
After you are a gamer
你是游戏玩家之后
Although he didn't say
虽然他没说
but i can feel it
但是我能感觉得到
He believes in you
他很相信你
Even want to stop you
甚至想拦住你
End Game
结束游戏
But I rejected it
但是被我拒绝了
why
为什么呀
we need you to cooperate with us
我们需要你配合我们
we believe you
我们相信你
Have the brains to deal with them
有头脑跟他们进行周旋
If it were my brother
要是我哥
It would be nice if you could say these things to me
能跟我说这些话就好了
This person
他这个人
All the words are hidden in the stomach
话都藏到肚子里
Even if it's bad, he won't say anything.
烂了他也不说
Very annoying
特别讨厌
That's how virtuous he is
他就这德行
I secretly forgive him
我都偷偷原谅他
several times
好几次了
That's right
没错
What's wrong
怎么了
How do you know my brother so well?
你怎么那么了解我哥
We are partners
我们是搭档啊
Just a partner
只是搭档
Right
也对
Just like him
就他那样的
You must not like it
你肯定看不上
correct
对了
You and Yao Yao
你跟姚瑶
Let’s quit the game together, right?
一起退出游戏了对不对
yes
是
but
但是
I could only do this at that time
当时我只能这么做
well-done
做得很好
Hide identity
隐藏身份
is the most important thing to you
是你最重要的事情
Catching spies is our business
抓间谍是我们的事情
Remember?
记住了吗
remember
记住了
Since they are thinking carefully
既然他们处心积虑
Want to drag you into the water
要拉你下水
I will definitely come to you again
就一定还会再来找你
Next
接下来
What should you do?
你该干什么干什么
live your life well
好好过你的生活
But you must be mentally prepared
但是一定要有心理准备
if they come to you again
如果他们再来找你的话
Never act rashly
绝不轻举妄动
I'll notify you when I have the opportunity
有机会通知你
1327099103
1327099103
My memory is pretty good
记忆力挺好呀
Worthy of being a level 28 player
不愧是二十八级玩家
You also play agent missions
你也玩特工任务
My level is not higher than yours
我等级没你高
Mr. Dana Wong
黄大拿先生
Then before we two
那咱俩之前
Have you seen it in the game?
是不是在游戏里见过
I know you
我知道你
but you don't know me
但是你不知道我
I see
我明白了
You were in the game before
你们之前就在游戏里
Start investigating me
开始调查我了
Then am I
那我是不是
When will it be online?
什么时候上线
You all know
你们全知道啊